# Anh Nguyen

### Software Engineer Student - Web Developer

A logical and creative thinker who enjoys learning new languages, frameworks, and technologies in general, excited to be part of the future of the technology industry. The satisfaction of solving problems is what drives me to be a better programmer. A design background combined with the creative mind can be utilized for aligning pixel-perfect performant experiences goals when programming.

#### Minneapolis, MN

- **(**612) 203-8821
- ☑ a.nguyen0208@gmail.com
- anguyen.page

#### **EXPERIENCE**

# **Self-Employed** — Freelance Web-Designer and Developer

May 2020 - Current

- · Contributed to designing and building new websites, responsible for all the front-end work, responsiveness browsers and devices compatibility, and SEO.
- Proficient in HTML, CSS, JavasCript, Bootstrap, MongoDB, Gatsby.

# **WORKSHOP & Chicago Exhibit Productions, Inc.**— Freelance Designer

Aug 2018 - October 2018

- Redesigned the space from sketch to 3D model; including inspirations, materials, and product display.
- Created graphics for the model to make a realistic feel of the space.

# **Exhibit Partners,LLC.** — Exhibit Design Intern

May 2017 - July 2017

- Developed new concepts for welcoming spaces, as well as improve and expand upon existing design areas.
- $\boldsymbol{\cdot}$  Sketched and designed a proposal concept for Tabasco's exhibit space by using the beMatrix frame system.

#### **EDUCATION**

# **University of St. Thomas** — *M.S Software Engineering*

2019 - December 2021 (expected)

# **Bemidji State University** — Bachelor of Science, Design

2013 - 2018

#### **SKILLS**

#### Languages

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Java, Python, SQL

#### Libraries/Framework

ReactJS, GatsbyJS, Gulp, Node.js, GraphQL, MySQL, SQL Oracle, ExpressJS, MongoDB

#### Tools

Git, MongoDB Atlas, MongoDB Compass, Postman, IntelliJ IDE, Illustrator, InDesign. Photoshop, After Effect, XD

# **PROJECTS**

#### Poncho.club

Oct 2020 - Nov 2020

Website designed and developed using Gatsby, Netlify, Node.js, and github.

# <u>portfolio</u>

May 2020 - July 2020

Personal portfolio website using Gulp.js and deploy with gh-pages.

## **Financial Calculator**

Sep 2019 - Oct 2019

Desktop application designed and developed for Intermediate Java course.